EVGENIY SULIM



Contacts

github.com/evgeniy210191

⋈ bees127@ukr.net

> +38 (066) 923 16 38

Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

English (A1)

Summary

Hello, I'm Eugene, I'm 32 years old, I'm disabled. I want to become an IT professional. Now I am looking for a company that will help me in my professional growth and open up opportunities for me to develop in this area. In turn, I guarantee reliable, long-term cooperation with high returns and focus on results. Yes, I do not have much practical experience and I do not know much, but I am ready to work, learn and develop for the benefit of the company (and mine).

Skills

HTML SASS adaptive site
CSS webpack JavaScript
Git parsel React.js (in the process of studying)

Experience

eleksacademy March 2022 - July 2022

Ukrainian it-scool January 2022 - May 2022

Go-it December 2023 - May 2023

Education

Kharkiv National University of Construction and Architecture, faculty of Sanitary Engineering, specialty - heat and gas supply and ventilation, 2013